Once upon a time, there was a sad love that would never be requited.
But that alone does not give birth to a story.
The man charged with the task of spinning this tale of love was no longer of this world.
The story lives on with the love forever immersed in sorrow.
Having lost its storyteller, the story is now wandering in search of its conclusion.
Impressive. Truly a prodigy.
Will a day come when I can dance like that too?
Whoa, you finally got your head straight!
What a wildly whimsical dream!
That's the spirit, Dad!
Molly is your strong suit!
Pattern and dream big, right?
Then you'll have bigger failures!
Work hard and things work out!
For normal people!
Yeah, well, for now you gotta get out of that probationary class!
That's right. When I'm Princess Tutu, I can dance any dance I want.
What? But is that me? Or someone else?
I'm just a girl in a probationary class.
Or rather, when you get down to it, I'm just a duck.
Maybe there's no point in me practicing.
Oh?
hundred bucks in my room!
Let's go!
You, baby!
You're PengshDBQ!
I'm so obsessed with this.
Watch out!
Who are you? Are you calling to me?
Fakir?
What's with that look?
Huh? What look?
What were you thinking?
What?
Just now, what were you thinking?
Someone. Someone's calling me.
I don't know who it is, but I feel like I can understand what that person's feeling.
The heartache deep down.
A desire to see someone and talk to them.
Feelings that I have too.
Could this possibly be what it feels like to be lonely?
What it feels like to be lonely?
Muto's regaining his heart.
Look at this face!
I hate this face and its feelings.
This wretched face wallowing in its loneliness.
Is it fun recalling such emotions?
Does it feel good, Muto?
No.
Right. You have no need of a heart, Muto. None whatsoever.
If you were to regain such a thing.
If I were.
Don't fall for such a fool's hope.
Got that?
Yes.
Speak louder.
Understood.
I will do as you say, Fakir.
Good. As it should be.
Miss Duck, as punishment for disturbing the advanced class, you will practice the develope. Am I understood?
Yes, sir.
If you practice earnestly, I'll put you back with the beginners.
Oh, yes, sir.
Practice poorly, though.
And I'll have you marry me forthwith!
I'm a bird on probation, plus I have to stay late.
At this rate, I may never get to be like Rue.
Oh, it's Muto.
Princess Tutu.
That's just a story.
She's still a princess fated, never to be with her prince.
When she confesses her love, she turns into a speck of light and vanishes.
That's just what happens to Tutu in the story.
The story isn't reality.
Though it is true that Muto is a prince from inside a story.
Oh, who cares?
It doesn't matter if the story is real or not.
All I want to do is find the pieces of Muto's heart and give them back to him.
That's right.
I'm not thinking about being with him or confessing to him or anything.
I'm not thinking about any of that!
I don't really understand.
It's okay. You can be a dummy, Muto. Now and forever.
Trust me, Muto. You do love me.
Oh, okay. Then I do love you.
Yes. Yes, remember that.
You don't need to understand. And you don't need a heart either.
What?
This feeling of wanting to see someone and talk to them.
It stays even when I'm with you.
Could this possibly be the feeling of loneliness?
I don't know. These emotions I'm feeling.
Room!
Would you please stop making him recall stupid things?
Muto, go back to your room.
Okay.
You'd better not be the person who's helping him dredge up these weird things.
Oh, please.
Who else are you saying could have done it?
Maybe it was Princess Tutu from the fairy tale. Maybe she appeared in real life.
Quiet. Try to stay away from Muto from now on.
Stop trying to order me around.
Huh? Piano? Where's Tuck?
Is that Tuck?
Oh, why are you two here?
Hey, hey, that's our line.
That's right. We came here thinking you would be really depressed because you had to stay behind.
Why are you so chipper?
Thank you both. But I'm really having a lot of fun right now.
Because the more you practice dancing, the more fun it becomes.
You don't!
Don't force it!
You can act sad when you're sad or like you're in pain when you're suffering.
Oh, you were suffering then.
Well, it was your fault.
No.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Say, why don't we keep her company?
Huh?
Yeah, good idea.
What?
Th-thank you.
It's fine. After all, this is for you.
Okay, let's all drop the probationary class with Duck.
You still have a long way to go, Duck.
Oh.
Miss Duck!
M-Mr. Cat!
I have some unfortunate news.
M-Unfortunate news?
Yes, Miss Duck.
You have worked much too hard. Therefore, unfortunately, I must put off having you marry me!
Uh, oh, I see then.
And?
I will let you return to the beginner class.
What?
Uh?
Uh, thank you so much!
You did it!
I'm so happy for you!
Good job!
All right!
Go!
The wind's picking up.
Hm?
Oh, Muto!
What is it you want me to do?
Who are you talking to?
W-what was...
Uh...
Muto?
Huh?
Where...
Muto!
Uh, he's gone.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
He's...
Not there!
Were you just calling for Muto?
Uh...
Yeah.
You need something?
No, not need.
But...
I just saw him come out this way.
What?
There was no one coming out.
B-but I'm sure I saw Muto!
No way.
I didn't see anyone out here.
So...
That way then?
It was you.
Huh?
You cried out rudely when I was dancing and interrupted me.
Oh!
Well that was...
You don't seem to have the slightest comprehension as to how much focus is required when dancing.
Oh!
If it's about that, sorry!
But more importantly, Muto is acting weird just now.
Or rather acting strange.
That's the same.
But anyway, I gotta find him now!
See ya!
Hold on!
We aren't done talking yet!
Wait just a minute!
Muto!
You need to stay away from Ruu.
Muto?
It's strange.
Definitely strange.
After talking to someone invisible, it's like time skipped forward and Muto...
I wonder which way he went.
Uh...
Ruu?
Your...
Your name...
It's stuck, right?
You run pretty...
Pretty fast!
Yeah!
I know!
Don't mock me!
I'm just a little out of breath, okay?
So just...
Cut it out!
Okay!
Sorry!
Oh!
What is it?
Since there are two of us here, I was thinking maybe it'd be faster if we split up and search
separately.
That's true!
You're quite right.
It's rather odd that someone like you and I should be walking shoulder to shoulder to
begin with.
Odd?
Yeah, she's right.
Oh!
Well, I'll go look over here.
We can decide on a time or something and meet up somewhere.
I changed my mind!
What?
Why is that?
It's much more reliable with two pairs of eyes looking.
Hmm...
Ya think?
Um...
What is it now?
Have you been friends with Mewto for a long time now?
You keep calling him Mewto.
That's awfully forward of you.
But Mewto told me that I could.
And another thing.
We're not exactly friends, so I'd appreciate it if you didn't call me Roo.
Then what am I supposed to call you?
Lady Roo.
Hmm...
Lady...
Roo?
What?
What's so hard about that?
It's just weird.
I'll call you Roo.
It's cuter that way.
Cuter?
Besides, we've walked together and talked all this time, so we're already friends now.
Thus it's Roo.
Still no Mewto.
Huh?
What?
I'll call you Roo.
It's cuter that way.
Cuter?
Besides, we've walked together and talked all this time, so we're already friends now.
Thus it's Roo.
Still no Mewto.
Huh, Roo?
Hmph.
What's that?
They're all...
all crying.
It's a funeral, so naturally.
Mewto!
Huh?
What?
What's this?
A dead end?
What can this be now?
Good evening, Rue. How is it that you know my...
Oh, she knows everything, even the fact that I'm a bird...
Oh.
Say what?
Anyway, she's nobody suspicious.
She is, too.
Miss Adol, we were looking for Muto and we saw him here, but something really weird happened just now.
He walked into that dead end with the funeral procession and vanished.
A story in a story.
Huh? A story?
There once was a beautiful maiden with a beautiful heart, and maidens fall in love.
Your story has nothing to do with finding Muto.
But unlike her beloved, this maiden was not noble-born. It was a love never to be requited.
I just said...
Wait, Rue. So what happened to the maiden, Miss Adol?
Devastated, she took her own life.
If her love wouldn't be requited in this world, she'd be reborn and see it fulfilled then.
However, her fiancé never came, and the maiden took another man to the world of the dead in his stead.
This is the maiden's melancholy story within the story.
Here in this town, there was a maiden who met the exact same fate.
As in the story, she fell in love.
And just as in the story, she lost hope.
And just as in the story, she took her own life, and then...
Is the story going to become real?
The story will become real in this town where reality and stories intermingle.
Just as in the story, Muto will be taken and that man's dead.
I won't let that happen.
It's starting.
Huh?
The dead end!
A mansion?
The maiden soul has settled in that mansion's courtyard.
She has been waiting.
Let's go, Rue!
Yes!
Muto!
I'm that man?
If you say it is true, then perhaps I am.
Muto, who are you talking to?
What's going on?
Is she the maiden then?
The pendant?
So it was you that was calling to me all of this time.
The rosemary from Giselle?
You mustn't take it!
No, Ruth!
They'll be taken away to the world of the dead!
Come over here!
Oh, Ruth!
Oh!
Come over here!
There she is!
Oh!
No, Ruth!
Whoa!
I don't have the stamina to dance Giselle to the end.
If only I'd done more basic training.
Bill!
No, don't!
No!
Oh, no!
Well, well, at this rate,
the prince will be entering an eternal slumber.
Is that okay, Princess Tootoo?
Hahaha!
My prince! Stop! You mustn't take it!
Ugh!
Why? Why do you interfere? Who are you?
I am Princess Tootoo.
Just like you,
I am fated never to be with the one whom I love.
Please, come and dance with me.
No bhole.
Amazing. She's still keeping up with her.
If you share the same fate as I, then why is your dancing not laden with sorrow?
Because of the many other emotions in my heart that won't give in to the sorrow.
Even if you take MUTO, it won't dispel the sorrow, will it?
Because the sorrow that resides within you is not how you truly feel.
I cannot know how much nor how long you have suffered.
But I know whatever your story is, you have grieved enough in your heart.
And so you can sleep in peace now.
Yes, you needn't grieve anymore.
This is the shard of your heart called sorrow, and it makes people suffer.
But it still is an important emotion to have.
Princess Tutu.
The emotions returning to the prince are loneliness and sorrow, feelings people have no desire for.
My dear Princess Tutu, do you think this will bring your prince happiness?
He he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he he...
Subscribe to Marcos TV
Release
Creator
Star
War
干 her
Mewto, he's a prince.
Is this the real you Mewto?
Will you be gone tonight, Duck?
I was a fool for believing what Duck said.
When you were wandering, completely stripped of your memories,
I was the one who gave you the name of Mewto.
My only wish is to keep on shining for someone.
Somewhere along the way, I had simply become forgotten.
It's sad that they no longer need you,
but it's something that can't be helped.
All who love stories gather round.
Well there we go.
Well, we are getting an龍,
So we'll chief.
This is not true before youию,
setbacks in December 4th.
Through the night our mother,
a mother and 저 glad toano,
where our original daughter was from.
There we go.
We are starting with her mother-in-law.
Then there was her mother-in-law